[music]
Oh dear
[laughter] I
hope you all will have a
whole day experiencing the fun at V and the
parasai boat. It's so enjoyable
and friendly, spring is here, spring is here, spring is here,
spring has
fragrance [music] spring flowers come with
so much passion, love is so strong
[music] morning sunbeams morning sunbeams morning sunbeams
flowers, young sprouts know green
on the branches Cha cha cha.  [Music]
is blue.
[music]
you all the way to the
[music] all the vi
you and all the to the
[music]
to
L when
[music] [music]
[music]
Everybody's
[music] [music] [music] [music] [music
]
[music] [music]
Everybody
[music]
Block 2 28 points total of the
program 62 points
so that in two blocks the smoothie team
completely won
38 and 264 asked to complain
[music]
Champion understand
Happ.
[music]